Moore, Frank C.; Papers apap223
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Correspondence and Subject File, 1896-1978; 6; 6 cubic ft.
  - National Graduate University, 1970 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 23)
  - National Health Council, 1957-1958 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 24)
  - National League of Cities, 1970 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 25)
  - National Municipal League, 1959-1961 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 26)
  - National Planning Association, 1971-1974 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 27)
  - National Tax Association, 1971-1973 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 28)
  - News & Views (American Society for Public Administration Newsletter), 1972-1973 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 29)
  - News Clippings on Committees & Commissions, 1954-1960 (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 30)
  - News Clippings on Frank C. Moore [Folders 1-3 of 5], 1940s-1960s; 3 folders (Box 25 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 31-33)
  - News Clippings on Frank C. Moore [Folders 4-5 of 5], 1940s-1960s; 2 folders (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 1-2)
  - News Clippings on Frank C. Moore, 1950-1961 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings on Frank C. Moore, 1953-1955 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings on Frank Moore, 1962-1970 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 5)
  - New Towns, 1971 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 6)
  - New York Central Railroad, 1972 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 7)
  - New York State Department of Commerce, Undated (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 8)
  - New York State Department of Education, 1940-1968 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 9)
  - New York State Office for the Aging, 1971 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 10)
  - New York State Political Campaigns, 1950; clippings (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 11)
  - New York State Political Campaigns, 1954 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Notes & Clippings, 1972 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 13)
  - Office of legislature Research - Press Releases, 1970 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Outdoors & Conservation, 1948-1960; clippings (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Outdoors & Conservation, 1943-1962; clippings (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 16)
  - P - General, 1959-1972 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Parmelee, Foster, 1956 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 18)
  - Per Capta Aid, 1969 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Politics - Campaign, 1956 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Photographs, [1940s-1960s]; 4 folders (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 21-24)
  - Politics - Campaign, 1958 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 25)
  - Politics - Campaign Mailings, 1966 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 26)
  - Politics - Charles Lanigan for Comptroller, 1966 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 27)
  - Politics - Congratulatory Messages, 1968 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 28)
  - Politics - News Releases, Leaflets, Clippings, etc., 1958-1968 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 29)
  - Politics - Party Platforms, 1966 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 30)
  - Politics - Political Contributions, 1968-1971 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 31)
  - Politics, Schools of, 1955 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 32)
  - Presidential Elections, 1968 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 33)
  - Public Service Commission, 1930 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 34)
  - Q - General, 1970-1972 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 35)
  - Rennie, James, 1951-1965 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 36)
  - Research Institute Recommendations, 1968-1969 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 37)
  - Resource Material - Articles & Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 38)
  - Retirement Messages, 1969 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 39)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1957-1958 (Box 26 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 40)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1958-1970 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - News Clippings, 1958 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Governor Nelson A. - Press Releases, 1971 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 3)
  - Rotary Club of Kenmore, 1947-1964 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 4)
  - S - General, 1954-1972; 2 folders (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 5-6)
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 1965 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 7)
  - School Boards Association, 1960-1963 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 8)
  - School Districts, 1959 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook - General (Folder 1 of 3), 1911-1971 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 10)
    Includes Letter from Gov. Dewey.
  - Scrapbook - General (Folder 2 of 3), 1911-1971 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 11)
    Includes Letters from Robert Moses & Henry Kissinger.
  - Scrapbook - General (Folder 3 of 3), 1911-1971 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook - General, 1966-1968; 2 folders (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 13-14)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1958-1960 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Speeches - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 16)
  - Speech List, Undated (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 17)
  - State University, 1948-1965 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 18)
  - St. Croix, 1969 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Steever Memorial, 1955 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Syracuse University - Honorary Degree, 1948 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 21)
  - Towns, Committee on, 1956 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 22)
  - Trustees of the Town & County Officers Training School, 1958-1962 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 23)
  - U - General, 1966-1971 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 24)
  - Weyerhaeser, Undated (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 25)
  - Wheeler, G. Doris, 1955 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 26)
  - Who's Who, 1944-1968 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 27)
  - Wilcox House Project, 1968 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 28)
  - Witmer, Ralph W., 1958-1969 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 29-30)
  - Wiretapping, 1956 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 31)
  - Woodstoves, Undated (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 32)
  - XYZ - General, 1954-1972 (Box 27 (6-General Correspondence and Subject File), Folder 33)
  - Photographs (oversized), 1940s-1960s (Oversized 55, Folder 3)
    - a. Frank Moore, Governor Thomas Dewey and unidentified man, 1940s-1950s?
    - b. Frank Moore at desk, ca. 1940s?
    - c. Frank Moore, Governor Thomas Dewey, Samuel Seabury and Nathan L. Miller at 150th Anniversary of State Comptroller's Office Commemorative Dinner, 1946
    - d. State Association of Towns ceremonial dinner, ca. 1930s?
- State University of New York, 1949-1973; 7; 3.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains records related to Moore's service as Chairman of the Board of Trustees of the State University of New York. It is arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically. It includes extensive files of clippings, Moore's dayfiles from 1958 through 1965, a large collection of memoranda received by Moore in his capacity as Chairman, material on various presidential search committees, assorted SUNY publications, and individual files on various subjects.
  - 25th Anniversary Celebration, 1973 March 13 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 1)
  - A Critique of Carl W. Engel - Hart's Unpublished The State University of New York: A Decade of Growth, 1958 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 2)
  - "An Analytical Comparison of the Systems of Higher Education in New York and California" by Freda Martens, 1963 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 5)
  - Board - Statement - Blegen Report, 12/12/1957 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 6)
  - Bond Issue, 1957; 1966-1969 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 7)
  - Bricks and Mortarboards: A Report on College Planning and Building, [1965?] (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Law School 75th Anniversary Speech, 1962 November 17 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 9)
  - Capital Construction Report, 1959 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 10)
  - Clipping and Talking Points for Interview, 1966 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 11)
  - Clippings for Board of Trustees, 1960 January (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 12)
  - Clippings for Board of Trustees, 1960 January-1960 February (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 13)
  - Clippings for Board of Trustees, 1960 March-1960 April (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 14)
  - Clippings for Board of Trustees, 1960 May (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 15)
  - Clippings for Board of Trustees, 1960 September-1960 November (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 16)
  - Clippings for Board of Trustees, 1960 October-1960 December (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1952 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1954 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1955 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1956 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1957 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1959 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 23)
  - Clippings, 1961; 2 folders (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 24-25)
  - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 26)
  - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 27)
  - Clippings, 1964; 4 folders (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 28-31)
  - Clippings (Folders 1-3 of 4), 1965; 3 folders (Box 28 (7-State University of New York), Folder 32-34)
  - Clippings (Folder 4 of 4), 1965 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1969 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 3)
  - Clippings, general, Undated (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 4)
  - Clippings - Long Island College, 1955-1956 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 5)
  - Clippings - Student Unrest at SUNY - Buffalo, 1970 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 6)
  - Committee to Save the State University, 1949 March 26 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 7)
  - Corning Community College, 1956-1960 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - General, 1956-1957 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Moore Letters re: Retirement from SUNY Board of Directors, 1965 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence re: Disposition of Moore's Files, 1969-1970 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence re: Biography of Austin Flint, 1961-1965 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence re: Retirement from SUNY Board of Trustees, 1965 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 14)
  - Crary, John C., Jr., Legal Counsel, Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 15)
  - Crary, John C., Jr., Legal Counsel, Opinions, 1959-1966 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 16)
  - Chairman's Dayfile, 1958 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 17)
  - Chairman's Dayfile, 1959 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 18)
  - Chairman's Dayfile, 1960 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 19)
  - Chairman's Dayfile, 1961 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 20)
  - Chairman's Dayfile, 1962 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 21)
  - Chairman's Dayfile, 1963 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 22)
  - Chairman's Dayfile, 1964 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 23)
  - Chairman's Dayfile, 1965 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 24)
  - Dr. Hamilton's Resignation, 1962 October-1962 November (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 25)
  - Evaluation of Proposed Sites for the State University of New York at Buffalo (Robert Heller Associates, Inc., Cleveland), 1967 February 01 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 26)
  - Finances, 1967 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 27)
  - Futures: The State University of New York and Your Children, 1965[?] (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 28)
  - George Hinman Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 29)
  - Governor Averill Harriman, 1957 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 30)
  - The Graduate School of Public Affairs: The Road Ahead, 1963 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 31)
  - The Harvests of Knowledge: A Report on Research Potentials and Problems in the State University of New York, 1957 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 32)
  - Howard Palfrey Jones Correspondence, 1962; 1965 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 33)
  - Master Plans, 1950-1964 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 34)
  - "Meeting the Increasing Demand for Higher Education in New York State", 1960 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 35)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence to Dr. Hamilton, 1959-1963 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 36)
  - Memoranda to Chairman, 1958 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 37)
  - Memoranda to Chairman, 1959 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 38)
  - Memoranda to Chairman, 1960 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 39)
  - Memoranda to Chairman, 1961 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 40)
  - Memoranda to Chairman, 1962 (Box 29 (7-State University of New York), Folder 41)
  - Memoranda to Chairman, 1963 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 1)
  - Memoranda to Chairman, 1964 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 2)
  - Memoranda to Chairman, 1965 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 3)
  - Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1964 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 4)
  - National Planning Association, 1967 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 5)
  - New York City Community College Day Division Catalog, 1965-1966 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 6)
  - President Gould's Inauguration, 1965 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 7)
  - Presidential Search, 1958; 2 folders (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 8-9)
  - Presidential Search, 1962-1963; 2 folders (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 10-11)
  - Program - Inauguration of Chancellor Boyer, 1971 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 12)
  - Program - Inauguration of Edward E. Palmer as President of the College of Forestry, 1970 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 13)
  - Progress and Reappraisal: State University of New York Report of the Chancellor, 1967-1968 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 14)
  - Reaction to F.C. Moore Interview in Knickerbocker News, March 26 and 27, 1963, by Freda Martens (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 15)
  - Regents Plan for Postwar Education in the State of New York, 1944 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 16)
  - The Regents Statewide Plan for the Expansion and Development of Higher Education, 1964 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 17)
  - Report on College Scholarships, 1955 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 18)
  - Report on Expansion Plans at SUNY - Buffalo, 1967 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 19)
  - Report - Handicapped Accessibility, 1967 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 20)
  - Report of the Temporary Commission on the Need for a State University, 1948 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 21)
  - Resignation of President Carlson, 1958 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 22)
  - Resolution re: Dr. William S. Carlson Resignation (3 Deans), 02/13/1958 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 23)
  - Retirement, 1964-1965 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 24)
  - School of Criminology (Criminal Justice), 1962-1965 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 25)
  - Selection Committee, Undated (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 26)
  - Selection Committee, 1958 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 27)
  - Selection Committee - Candidate Biographies, Undated (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 28-29)
  - Selection Committee - Correspondence, 1963; Undated (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 30)
  - Selection Committee - Memoranda, 1962; 1963; Undated (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 31)
  - Selection Committee - Primary and Supplementary Lists, Undated (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 32)
  - The Shaping of a University: State University of New York Report of the President, 1965-1966 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 33)
  - Speakers, Policy on, 1962 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 34)
  - State Education Law Excerpts, 1955-1964 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 35)
  - State University at Buffalo Alumni News, 1969-1970 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 36)
  - State University Newsletter, 1967 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 37)
  - State University Newsletter, 1968 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 38)
  - State University Newsletter, 1969 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 39)
  - State University of New York(Report), 1950 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 40)
  - State University of New York News, 1970 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 41)
  - State University of New York News, 1971 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 42)
  - State University of New York Summary Bulletin, 1965 Spring (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 43)
  - Studies of Public School Support 1967 Series: The Urban Education Crisis - Some Fiscal Considerations, 1968 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 44)
  - SUNY Buffalo Reporter, 1970 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 45)
  - Supplementary Statement by the Committee on Four-Year Colleges of the Board of SUNY, 1950 February (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 46)
  - University of Buffalo Alumni News, 1969 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 47)
  - University Review, Vol. 1 No. 1, 1966 Fall (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 48)
  - Wells Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 49)
  - Where New York Is - There Is State University, 1954 (Box 30 (7-State University of New York), Folder 50)
  - Board of Regents Convocation, 1966; Oversized (Box 54 (7-State University of New York), Folder 1)
  - Capital Construction and Finance, 1966-1968; Oversized (Box 54 (7-State University of New York), Folder 2)
  - Capital Construction and Finance, 1966-1968; Oversized (Box 54 (7-State University of New York), Folder 3)
  - Clippings (Miscellaneous), 1949-1955; Oversized (Box 54 (7-State University of New York), Folder 4)
  - Governor Rockefeller, 1955-1969; Oversized (Box 54 (7-State University of New York), Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1969; Oversized (Box 54 (7-State University of New York), Folder 6)
  - Tuition, 1960-1961; 1969; Oversized (Box 54 (7-State University of New York), Folder 7)
  - Campus Plans for the State University of New York, 1965; Oversized (Box 55 (7-State University of New York), Folder 1)
- Conferences, Commissions and Committees, 1947-1971; 8
  This series contains records relating to Moore's service on a wide variety of conferences, commissions and committees. It is broken up into subseries by committee.
  - Committee on Constitutional Tax and Debt Limitations and City-School Fiscal Relations (CTDL-CSFR), 1947-1953; 8.1; 3 cubic ft.
    This series contains the records of the Committee on Constitutional Tax and Debt Limitations and City-School Fiscal Relations (CTDL-CSFR). It includes a wide range of materials, including the Committee's annually produced statistical binders on various topics, the records of the Committee's meetings, and subject binders on various subjects. It is organized alphabetically by subject.
    - Acknowledgements, Undated (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1)
    - Agenda & Notes, 1948-1949 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 2)
    - Agenda & Notes, 1950 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 3)
    - Agenda & Notes, 1951-1952 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 4)
    - Agenda & Notes, 1952-1953 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 5)
    - Charts & Debt, 1947-1948; binder (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 6)
    - City - School Fiscal Relations, 1947 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 7)
    - City - School Fiscal Relations, 1947-1948 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 8)
    - City - School Fiscal Relations, 1947-1949 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 9)
    - City - School Fiscal Relations, 1947-1952 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 10)
    - City - School Fiscal Relations, 1948-1949 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11)
    - City - School Fiscal Relations, 1948-1949; 2 folders (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12-13)